linkedin.com/in/ray-farandi github.com/rayfarandi

+62 85951626452 Cipayung/Kota Depok

Ray Farandi

I am a full-stack developer with a big curiosity for new things. I am experienced in developing web frontends using React, Tailwind, and Redux, and I fetch data using HTTP requests with Axios. On the backend, I am proficient in Node.js, Golang, and PostgreSQL for backend development. I'm always interested in learning more about programming languages and enjoy working both in teams and independently to achieve goals.

Skills

Javascript, Node JS, Golang, Express JS, React, Taillwind, Code Igniter, PHP, Wordpress, Networking

Project Experiences

- Cofee Shop Web APP
 - o is a coffee ordering application that was worked on for 8 weeks.
 - Application app, you can browse our menu and order your coffee, food, and pastries ahead of time.
 - o tech stack used: javascript, node js, express js, React, Redux, Tailwind
 - o is an individual project
 - o Github: Frontend, Backend
- VALLET Web APP
 - o is an application that was worked on for 2 weeks
 - e-wallet application
 - o tech stack used: javascript, node js, express js, React, Redux, Tailwind
 - o team project
 - o I'm in the frontend, working on the homepage, dashboard, mobile display
 - O Github: Frontend, Backend
- CinemaTix Web APP
 - o is an application that was worked on for 2 weeks
 - e-Ticket
 - o tech stack used: Go,Jwt,Gin, React, Redux, Tailwind
 - o team project
 - I'm in the frontend, working on the homepage, dashboard, mobile display
 - o Github: Frontend, Backend
- Web PT.Nuklir Indonesia Laboratorium (PT.NUKLINDOLAB)
 - o Portfolio PT
 - o tech stack used: Html, javascript, css, wordpress.
 - Individual
 - O Link: Visit
- Web PT.Karya Sentosa Unggul (PT.KSU)
 - Portfolio PT
 - o tech stack used: React ,javascript, Tailwind.
 - o Individual
 - O Link: Visit

Work Experiences

• NUKLINDOLAB, IT Staff

Juli 2018 - Agu 2023

- Manage Internet, Lan, Wan.
- Manage Telephone IP PABX
- Manage Server Cloud Data

- Manage Security Network
- Manage Laboratory Application Server

• PT.KARYA SENTOSA UNGGUL, IT Staff

Mei 2017 - Juni 2018

- Manage Internet, Lan, Wan.
- Install and configure new hardware and software
- Maintain and update IT systems and software

Education

• Fazztrack, Full Stack Web & Golang
Completing intermediate Backend using Node JS, Express JS, Golang
Completing intermediate Frontend using React, tailwind, Redux

Okt 2023 - Apr 2024

• Universitas Gunadarma, Sistem Informasi

Sep 2015 - Agu 2017

o Grade Point Average (GPA): 3.05

Honor and Award

- Web Master by Dumet School May 2021
- ISO/IEC 17043:2010 Conformity assessment General requirements for proficiency testing by AN-Training & Consulting Desember 2021
- MikroTik Certified Network Associate MTCNA by Mikrotik-Academy June 2020
- Installation Computer Network Training And Certificate at Professional Certification Body by BBPLK Agustus Oktober 2017
- Building Networking With Cisco by Universitas Gunadarma 2015